vpnsp.com 2013-05-01

# Vpnsp.com Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY - COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At VPN Service Providers (VPNSP), we want to make your experience on our site both enjoyable and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. 

INFORMATION VPNSP GATHERS AND TRACKS

VPN Service Providers gathers two types of information about users:

VPN Service Providers Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:

Optional Voluntary Information

We may choose to offer free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users.

Usage Ttracking

VPNSP tracks user traffic patterns throughout the site. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. We do break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).

Privacy Policy Use __

 _How the information you gather is used if relevent._

USE OF INFORMATION

VPNSP uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on the site, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums.

SHARING OF THE INFORMATION

VPNSP uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help us better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to continue offering quality content to our visitors. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

OPT-OUT POLICY

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:
